stlawu.edu 2019-04-15

# Web Privacy Statement | St. Lawrence University

St. Lawrence University (the University) respects the privacy of the people who use [www.stlawu.edu](http://www.stlawu.edu/). This privacy statement informs visitors about information this website collects, who may access that information, and what the University may do with the collected information. The University reserves the right to make changes to this web privacy statement.

The University uses cookies and web analytics services to track user activity on the institution’s main website. This information is used to track usage, analyze trends in user behavior, and to personalize the experience for individual users. Users may accept or reject cookies by configuring their browser security settings appropriately.

The University may occasionally collect information via the website. The University is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell information to outside entities, but we reserve the right to share it with strategic partners who are bound to confidentiality agreements with the University.

Update 2018:  As defined in the European Union General Data Protection Regulation (the "GDPR"), "personal data  generally means any information that can be used to identify a natural person.  If you are in the European Union, or if your personal data otherwise is subject to the GDPR, you should understand that the University will use out technical infrastructure in the United States to deliver various services to you. 

In order to fulfill our responsibilities with you (if you are an applicant, student, employee, or if you are purchasing items from us, browsing our website, etc.) we may need to transfer your Personal Data to the United States, and possibly to other jurisdictions outside of your home country, as necessary to provide these services. Similarly, if you are browsing our webpage, we may collect certain Personal Data about you (for example, your ISP address) in order to enhance our webpage, and your experience on our webpage, in accordance with our GDPR PRIVACY NOTICES below. Collection and processing of your Personal Data as you browse our webpage is necessary for our legitimate interests, and we believe these interests will not interfere with your fundamental rights or freedoms.

## GDPR PRIVACY NOTICES

If you have questions about this statement, or about how the University uses any information collected via its website, contact Director of Digital Communictions Mark Mende [mmende@stlawu.edu](mailto:mmende@stlawu.edu) or Vice President for Community and Employee Relations Lisa Cania [lcania@stlawu.edu ](mailto:lcania@stlawu.edu)
